So guys, welcome to another video.
So in this video, we are going to learn how to dump Elsa's using the mini cats.
So we all know mini cats is one of her team tools.
And often it was used by the protectors to dump current shells are doing further activities
like post-expirations.
This is one of our powerful tools.
So let me show you how to do, let me show you how to do that, open up TMD and help redirect
to the download directory first.
So I have already downloaded the mini cats binary.
So we will be getting from a GitHub repo.
So you don't need to compile or anything, so you can find the mini cats.dx from there.
So I have one of our site, it's a cheat sheet of for mini cats.
So it's looking pretty nice, okay?
So the website is up to cosics.2.com, the mini cats cheat sheet, okay?
So from this also, you can able to dump Elsa's key grades, okay?
Let me execute the LSA dump is used to SAM command, so before executing you need to execute
the mini cats.
So you can see there's another terminal has been opened by the mini cats.
So let me paste the mini a sec, let me copy this and let me paste this.
So I was getting some errors, like LSA's TMD user SAM key, let me execute another command
in our system privilege, so we know how to do that.
We already developed a program to escalating the privilege from administrator to the system.
Let me find bin logon, and so let me execute the store constealer.
And now I will be redirecting to the downloads directory, okay?
So now I'll try to execute the LSA's dump, let me execute the privilege debug first, okay?
So whether we have enough privilege or not, now it's 20, okay, execute this two, elevating
the token, and let me now execute the process SAM, so now it was working properly.
Let me show some of the credentials here.
So you can see a user called us an administrator, so here's a hash, a NLM hash of an administrator,
so I'm copying the NLM hash of the administrator, and I'll be moving to the NLM crack
online, so here you can find a separate upside, the crackstation.net, let me click on the
capture, and so now it cracked my password, like the NLM hash results to the password, the
administrator password was on password, let me move back to there, also we have some other
credentials to, let me search out that, so here you can see another one user named as an
attack, and let me check this user hash, user password, the attacker user password as a
ABCD123, so this is the attacker user password, and yeah, so this is how you can play with
the mimic here, so else has some secrets, let me execute this, so here you can find the
DPA related DPA system and default password, yeah, it's kind of a secret dump, let me
execute the LCS catch, so these are some of this, this mimic at this one of a powerful tool
to extract a credential from the machine, it will be very useful when you are dealing with
some active directory based attacks, there is sort of option you can, you can use to get a
credential, so yeah, we played a few of the commands using the elker, sorry, using the
mimic ads, so now I hope we are clear about the mimic ads, so by using the mimic ads also
we can dump an else as, okay, so this command is also using use to extract the password,
so this command was giving some error results, okay, maybe your system will cooperate to execute
this command, let's try that, okay, so yeah, that's all about the video, let's hop off
and I will see you in the next video, thank you, bye, bye.